[{"answer": " I am so worried about my college applications", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Why?  What happened", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 14, "question": " I am so worried about my college applications", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Well, I sent my applications off four weeks ago, and I havent heard anythin", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Why?  What happened", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " How many did you apply to", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Well, I sent my applications off four weeks ago, and I havent heard anythin", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Five", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 20, "question": " How many did you apply to", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Well, I wouldnt worry about it yet", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Five", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " No", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Well, I wouldnt worry about it yet", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Its still pretty early.  It takes a few months before you hear anything from th", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 23, "question": " No", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Why does it take so long", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Its still pretty early.  It takes a few months before you hear anything from th", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Think about it.  Most schools get thousands of applications each term.  They hav", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Why does it take so long", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " That makes sense.  I guess youre right", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Think about it.  Most schools get thousands of applications each term.  They hav", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " I didnt hear back from my school until four months had passed", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 37, "question": " That makes sense.  I guess youre right", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Oh, OK", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I didnt hear back from my school until four months had passed", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Did you check with the Admissions Office or the department to make sure the", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Oh, OK", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " No, I sent my applications registered mail, so I know that they have receive", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Did you check with the Admissions Office or the department to make sure the", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " That was smart.  At least you know they got the applications.  All you can do no", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 45, "question": " No, I sent my applications registered mail, so I know that they have receive", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " What if a long time passes and I dont hear from them", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 51, "question": " That was smart.  At least you know they got the applications.  All you can do no", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " I guess you could do a few things to check on it", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 52, "question": " What if a long time passes and I dont hear from them", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Like what", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 53, "question": " I guess you could do a few things to check on it", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " You could always email or call the Admissions Office or the departments too", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Like what", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " I tried calling the Admissions Office, but no one ever answers.  It just say", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " You could always email or call the Admissions Office or the departments too", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " You should.  Leave them a message and Im sure theyll get back to you.  Theyr", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 59, "question": " I tried calling the Admissions Office, but no one ever answers.  It just say", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I guess I should.  Ive sent 10 emails in the past week, but they never respond", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 63, "question": " You should.  Leave them a message and Im sure theyll get back to you.  Theyr", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Mariam!  You shouldnt do that.  Just send one email and wait for the response", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 64, "question": " I guess I should.  Ive sent 10 emails in the past week, but they never respond", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " But two days passed and they hadnt responded, so I resent the email an", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Mariam!  You shouldnt do that.  Just send one email and wait for the response", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " You really shouldnt do that.  Youre going to annoy them and they migh", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 69, "question": " But two days passed and they hadnt responded, so I resent the email an", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Maybe I was being too concerned", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 75, "question": " You really shouldnt do that.  Youre going to annoy them and they migh", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Well, dont worry about it.  Just be patient and give it more time.  If they got you", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Maybe I was being too concerned", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " OK.  Ill try to", "docId": "04-02", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Well, dont worry about it.  Just be patient and give it more time.  If they got you", "qSentId": 82}]
